

SUMMARY

Dedicated Web Developer, with strong knowledge in HTML, CSS and Typescript. Committed to creating beautiful and user friendly websites by applying my expertise in web technologies.

Dedicated to learning through practice and persistence.

In the interest of providing value for your company in addition to joining a motivated team with high expectations.

CONTACT

- niswtis@gmail.com
- (30) 6957160256
- https://niswtis.github.io/pe rsonalWebsite/
- in linkedin.com/in/aristidesnisotakis

Cooperation

SOFT SKILLS

- Logical thinking
- Adaptation
- Organisation
- Communication

LANGUAGES

- English(Level B2)
- Greek(Native)

Aristides **Nisotakis**

Web Developer

EXPERIENCE

Pluxbox, Hilversum, Netherlands



Apr 2021 - Sep 2022

Web Developer

- Co-supervised a four member team with the goal of creating websites for radio stations all over Europe.
- Developed multiple challenging Front-End DOM structures, such as an Electronic Program Guide and a Radio Rundown.
- Connected intricate systems with the logic of the expanding platform using Typescript, Node.js and APIs.
- Assisted in the development of the company's website in the pursuance of engaging with more clients

Pluxbox, Hilversum, Netherlands



Oct 2020 - Apr 2021

Intern Web Developer

- Gained traction with core web development technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, Typescript.
- Followed the project management process using the Scrum and Kanban Agile Frameworks.
- · Aligned with the code management flow using Git.
- Strengthened analytical skills in anticipation of the preset deadlines.

EDUCATION

Computer Science Department | 2015 - 2021

University of Crete

CERTIFICATES

Modern React with Redux [2023 Update] | 2023



Udemy

 Γ

Node with React: Full Stack Web Development | 2023

짆

Udemy

HARD SKILLS

- React.js
- HTML
- Typescript
- MongoDB

- Redux
- CSS
- Node.js
- Git